nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's tight.
ピチピチだ
Have you ever done that?
それ、したことあるんですか?
As for knowing play.
承知プレイとかは
Are you always lighthearted?
いつも軽心してる?
It's okay, I have good style.
大丈夫、スタイル良いから
Really good play.
本当に良いプレイ
nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's tight.
ピチピチだ
Have you ever done that?
それ、したことあるんですか?
As for knowing play.
承知プレイとかは
Are you always lighthearted?
いつも軽心してる?
It's okay, I have good style.
大丈夫、スタイル良いから
Really good play.
本当に良いプレイ
nice to meet you.
初めまして
Another beautiful person came.
また綺麗な人来てくれました
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you aiming to become a gay girl?
ゲイ子さん目指してるとか
It suits you.
似合うな
It definitely looks good on me.
絶対似合いそう
A gay boy.
ゲイ子さんが
The style is great, isn't it?
スタイル良いですよね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's true.
本当です
How old are you now?
今何歳だったかな?
Can I ask you to say it in the second half of the first half?
前半後半で言ってもらっていいですか?
I'm in my early 20s.
20代前半です
It's tight.
ピチピチだ
This was my first time making videos, and I had no experience in the water business.
本当にビデオとか初めてで、水商売とかも経験ないですもんね
Thank you very much for coming.
よく来てくれましたね
It sounds like you're probably interested in a lot of different things.
多分いろんなものの興味がありそうな感じですね
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
It took about two months to get there.
あるまでに大体2ヶ月くらいかかったんですね
that's right.
そうです
But wasn’t email amazing?
でもメールがすごかったじゃないですか?
The contents.
内容が
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Can I tell you?
言っちゃっていいですか?
Is it true?
本当なんですか?
Even I didn't know.
僕でもわからなかったけど
It's like walking around town with your phone on.
電話はめて街歩くみたいな
How dangerous is that?
なんてやばいんですかね
It's a well-known play.
周知プレイだよね
I agree.
そうですね
Have you ever done that?
そうしたことあるんですか?
Well-known play.
周知プレイとか
No, no.
いやいや
I'm not going home today.
今日は帰りませんよ
No, no.
いやいや
Can I ask you one thing?
1つ聞いていいですか?
How many people have experience?
経験人数はどれくらい?
Just a little bit.
ちょいちょいくらいです
occasionally?
ちょいちょい?
Hey, hey.
ちょ いちょい
All you need is one hand.
要は片手くらい
yes.
はい
You mean less than 5 people on one hand?
片手の5人以下ってこと?
About 10.
10ちょいくらい
A little over 10?
10ちょい?
That's what it is.
そういうことね
That's amazing.
すごいね
That's normal, these days.
普通だよね、今時ね
I don't know.
わかんないです
is that so.
そうですか
そう ですか
What do you think is going to happen?
何が起こるんだって感じですか?
Is there something you want to ask?
何か聞きたいことというか
Maybe it's just a little embarrassing.
多分ちょっと恥ずかしいだけです
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Because that's where we met earlier.
だってさっき会ったところもね
I agree.
そうですね
It was getting close, wasn't it?
近づいてきちゃいましたよね
My skin is getting worse.
僕は肌がなってますからね
I'm just as perverted as anyone else.
同じ人に負けなく変態なんですよ
That's right.
そうなんですね
Can I kiss you for a second?
ちょっとキスしてもいいですか?
that's right.
そうです
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
How many centimeters tall?
身長何センチ?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
That's low.
低いよね
How should I attack?
どう攻めていいんだ?
どう攻めたらいいかな?
I've already done it.
もうやっちゃった
Shall we sit down for a while?
ちょっと座ろうか
Hey, hey.
ちょ いちょい
Purple?
紫?
Pink with black lace.
ピンクに黒のレース
I'm that petty person.
僕はそのペッチだね
Do you want to cool down?
冷めたい?
Don't you want to get cold?
冷めたいわけないか
In secret.
秘密で
Just touch it
ちょっと触ってみ
hand.
て
Up to that point.
その とこまで
Are you always my boyfriend?
いつも彼氏にしてる?
yes.
はい
I played a prank on you.
いたずらしたよ
I'm starting to want to.
したくなってきたよ
Do these pants suit you?
このパンツ似合ってる?
Those are really nice pants.
すごく良いパンツだね
It's naughty.
エッチだよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
feeling
気持
Isn't it bad?
ち 悪くない?
It looks so bad.
こんな悪しそう
I can see it.
見えてるよ
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗だよ
Neverdolin is flying, right?
ネバードリン飛んでるでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
It smelled really good.
すご く良い匂いしてきた
すごく良い匂いしてきたよ
It smells really good.
すごく良い匂いしてる
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Shake your legs?
足を振る?
it hurts?
痛い?
it hurts.
痛い
It's not Ketar, is it?
ケータルじゃないですよね
Two of us.
僕たち2人
Because it's longy.
ロンギーだから
Come behind me for a moment.
ちょっと僕の背に来て
There's a picture of panties on it.
パンツの絵がかかるんだよ
It's coming on my back.
僕の背に来るんだよ
It smells good.
いい匂いするよ
it hurts.
痛い
TRUE?
本当?
first time?
初めて?
yes.
はい
It smells really good.
すごく良い匂い
It smelled really good.
本当に良い匂いしたね
I don't want to take it though.
取りたくないけどね
Take it slow.
ゆっくりとじゃあさ
Can I have it removed?
抜いてもらっていい?
抜 いてもらっていい?
Can I have it removed?
抜いてもらっていい?
Show me a little.
ちょっと見せて
Because it's okay.
大丈夫だから
After all, it had a very wet smell.
やっぱりすごい濡れる匂いがあったね
This is amazing.
これはすごいよ
I'll buy my pants later.
後で僕のパンツ買うからね
That's amazing.
すごいね
First.
最初にね
It hurts, right?
痛いでしょ?
It smells really bad.
匂いめっちゃするからね
Can I have you stand there for a moment?
そこの顔に一回ちょっと立ってもらってもいい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Because it has good style.
スタイル良いから
I haven't done anything yet.
まだ何もしてないのにね
Let's sleep like this.
こんな感じで寝ちゃおう
Is it a little special?
ちょっと特別かな?
Even though I haven't done anything.
何もしてないのにね
A little bit drips here
少しはここ、垂れまく
That's it.
ってる
It's okay.
大丈夫 だね
I'm drawing with a camera.
カメラで描いてるよ
Should I do it a little earlier?
もう少し前にしちゃおうか
Can you go a little earlier?
もうちょっと前に行けるか?
Can we go a little earlier?
もう少し前に行けるか?
Can you go a little earlier?
もうちょっと前に行けるか?
Don't you want me to calm down now?
そろそろさ、 落ち着いて欲しくない?
Can I get some sleep?
ちょっと寝てもいい?
i want to sleep?
寝たい?
There are tears.
涙あるね
Look for it.
探して
Stick your hips out.
腰突き出してくれ
Please tell me to give you more blood.
血はもっと打ってくださいって言ってくれ
I'm full.
お腹いっぱい
I can see your waist.
腰 見えるよ
I can see the hole in your waist.
腰の穴見えてるよ
It's just the first one.
先一丁だけだよ
Warm.
あったかい
Please tell me to follow you.
ついてくださいって言ってくれ
I was able to use it.
使いできた
It's a really good project.
本当に良いプロジェクトだね
Really.
本当 に
Can I come in?
入っていい?
I'll go.
行くよ
Please show me a little.
ちょっと見せてね
How was the shooting?
撮影どうでした?
It was embarrassing.
恥ずかしかったです
Thank you again.
またお願いします